Guide to the Yale Library Associates Gift Memoranda
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Library Associates gift memoranda
1946-1983
RU 734
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
(1 box)
The records consist of memoranda, maintained by the Library Business Office, documenting gifts of the Yale Library Associates.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-C (YRG 32-C), Records of Yale University Library departments and offices.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted to the office of origin only.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of memoranda, maintained by the Library Business Office, documenting gifts of the Yale Library Associates.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject.
Libraries -- Gifts, legacies; Yale Library Associates; Yale University. Library
- Gift memos for Yale Library Associates, 1946-1983; Accession 1985-A-060
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to the office of origin only.
  - Gift memoranda, 1947, 1949, 1959-1962, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gift memoranda, 1946-1947, 1949-1950, 1952, 1961, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Correspondence 809A-50-74504, 1968 November - 1983 May (Box 1, Folder 6 - 8)
  - Gift Memos
    - 1966 Jan 12 - 1972 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 9 - 10)
    - 809A-50-74504, 1967 August - 1983 May (Box 1, Folder 11 - 13)
    - 845A-50-69010, 1969 June - 1971, 1975 - 1983 December (Box 1, Folder 14 - 16)
    - 1972 Jul 10 - 1976 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 17 - 18)
    - 1975 Jun 17 - 1983 Jun 17 (Box 1, Folder 19 - 20)
    - 1976 Jun 22 - 1979 Jun 21 (Box 1, Folder 21 - 22)
    - 1979 Jul 19 - 1981 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 23 - 24)